Guide to the Sterling Beckwith Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - A.O. Smith (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - MWD Tehachapi Report (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Louis Allis Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Louis Allis Balance Nic (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Louis Allis Seals & Gaskets (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Louis Allis Ameriblower Load Loss (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Louis Allis Vehicle (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Louis Allis Generator (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Louis Allis Magnetic Clutch Drawings (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Louis Allis Sonar (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Louis Allis Clutch Drawings (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Louis Allis HU Ins. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Louis Allis Clutch (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Louis Allis Freon (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Louis Allis American Synthetic (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Louis Allis Refrigeration Systems (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Louis Allis MAST (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Louis Allis Lakeland Pipeline (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Louis Allis Noise (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Louis Allis Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Louis Allis 1500kw 400~ (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Louis Allis (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Louis Allis Sales Brochures, GM Engineering Journal (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Louis Allis (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Louis Allis Sleeve Bearing Clutch (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Louis Allis Test Facilities (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Louis Allis Submersible Tests (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Louis Allis Propulsion (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Louis Allis Hermetic Motor Failures- Adhesives 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Louis Allis Freon (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Louis Allis Current (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Louis Allis Main Submarine Propulsion (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Louis Allis Mechanical Design (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Louis Allis Sonar 2 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Louis Allis Sonar 1 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Louis Allis Drawings (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Louis Allis Magnetic Clutch Calculations (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Louis Allis Syn-Ind Motors (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Marathon Correspondence 1962 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Marathon Correspondence 1961 2nd (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Marathon Correspondence 1961 1st (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Marathon Vibration Reports & Papers (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Marathon Drawings, Etc. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Marathon (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Marathon Notes (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Marathon Specs, Etc. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Marathon Test Data (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Marathon Test Data (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Paradise Irrigation District Hydroelectric Generator Financing (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Paradise PG&E Bills (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Paradise 1989 Statements (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Paradise 1986 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Quotes (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Permits (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Permits II (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Paradise PG&E Metering (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Investments vs. Returns (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Paradise Hydraulic Operator (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Paradise D Tank (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Paradise Insurance 1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Paradise C&D Tank Trip (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Paradise After 3/10/1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Insurance I (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Water Hammer (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Property Tax (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Instruction Book (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Controller- Miscellaneous – Nameplates (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Energy Efficient Motor Conversion (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Paradise E Tank Prospect (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Vibration Monitoring (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Paradise (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Paradise D Tank (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Photographs (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Paradise Final Photographs, C Tank (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Paradise Photographs 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Paradise After 9/29/1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Upper Dam Proposal (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Generators (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Reports (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Paradise (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Manuals (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Instruction Book (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Paradise PG&E Contract Negotiation 1983 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Paradise History Start Up 3/1983 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Paradise 1982-1987 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Paradise 1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Paradise 1987 Gen. Control (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Paradise C Tank (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Hydraulic Control (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Paradise P. OS 1983 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Paradise D Tank Costs 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Paradise D Tank Expenses 1986 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Paradise C Tank Expenses 1986 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Paradise D Tank II 1985 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Paradise PG&E (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Paradise C Tank Evaluation Computer (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Paradise PG&E Rates (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Expenses 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Expenses 1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Expenses 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Expenses 1988 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Paradise PG&E 1987 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Evaluation 1987 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Paradise Data Notebook (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Paradise C Tank Expenses 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Paradise D Tank Expenses 1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Paradise C Tank (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Paradise D Tank (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Seasonal Flows (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Efficient PR Valves (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Patents (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Paradise D Tank (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Summaries (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Paradise PG&E Meter Readings (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Paradise D Tank Charts 12/1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Insurance Contracts (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Paradise FERC 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Right of Way (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Paradise C Tank Annual Reports (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Paradise D Tank Annual Reports (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gooden, James – confidential (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Helicopter Patent 1961 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Helicopter Lab Work (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Helicopter Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Helicopter Correspondence, Drawings, References (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Helicopter Model 21 Specs (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Helicopter Model 20A (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Helicopter Drawings (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Helicopter Auth 7361 Design Data Costs (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Helicopter Reports (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Helicopter Motor Data & Articles (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Helicopter Designs (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Helicopter Costs & Orders (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - A-C Roy Rufus Lee Paper (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Beckwith Patents (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - A-C Patents (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Beckwith Patents (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Design Data (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Hydrogen Cooled Generator (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Beckwith Reports (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Standard Design Data (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - A-C Publications, Supercharger Articles (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Hydrogen Cooled Generator (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Brushless Exciter for 500w MIL (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Design & Test Data (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - A-C General Generator Design (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - A-C General Design (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - A-C Design Standards- Engineering Practice (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - A-C Design Miscellaneous II (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - A-C Saturation (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - A-C Saturation Core Calculations (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - A-C Core Loss, Etc. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - A-C Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Helicopter Polycopter Patent Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Helicopter Patents (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Helicopter Polycopter Official Patent & Related (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - A-C Patents 1968 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Beckwith Thesis 1929 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - A-C Saturation (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Westinghouse Norfolk (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Westinghouse Oroville (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Amortisseur Rocky Mount Sparking (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Westinghouse Trial (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - 4 Wheel Drive (Flex Shaft) (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Yuba - James Changaris (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Narrows Generator Thermocouple Voltage (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Glass Battery (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Glass Battery (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Glass Battery (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Glass Battery (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - A-C Fuel Cells 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Westinghouse Report & Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Beckwith Article & Typescript (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Louis Allis End Ring Stress (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Louis Allis Inductor (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Standard List of Turbos (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Turbo Summaries (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - PFL (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Design Text (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Design Data 1941 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Sound (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous II (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - A-C Scientists in Management (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Dual-Jet Patents (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Dual-Jet Air Curtain (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Dual-Jet Patents- Active (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Dual-Jet Jet Stream Match & Merryweather (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Dual-Jet Patents (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Dual-Jet New Patent 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Dual-Jet Patents (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Dual-Jet (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Dual-Jet MVS (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Dual-Jet References (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dual-Jet Air Curtain (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dual-Jet Air Door Crib (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Dual-Jet 502 Meter Flow (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Dual-Jet Air Doors 12/1972-3/1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Dual-Jet Patents- Japan (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Dual-Jet Litigation Patents (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Dual-Jet Air Curtain (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Dual-Jet Marine Reporter 4/1/1959 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Dual-Jet Patent Trial Infringement (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Dual-Jet Budget Projections (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Dual-Jet Air Mixing- Turbulence Tests (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dual-Jet Sherer-Pennant Pty. Ltd. Australia (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dual-Jet 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Dual-Jet Warren 10-11/1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dual-Jet Power Saving Meter & Data (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dual-Jet Air Jets in Mines (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Dual-Jet 1984-1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Dual-Jet Resco (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Dual-Jet Craig-Nicol (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Dual-Jet Hussman (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dual-Jet Electrolux (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Dual-Jet Hot Gas (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dual-Jet Mark VI Evaporation Tests (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dual-Jet Mark VI Coil (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Dual-Jet Fan Motors (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Dual-Jet Lab Projects 1972 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Dual-Jet Lab (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Dual-Jet Power Comparisons (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dual-Jet Craig-Nicol (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Dual-Jet Mark VII Design & Tests (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Dual-Jet Kysor Patent Disclosure 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Dual-Jet Kysor (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Dual-Jet (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Dual-Jet Evaluation of Multi-Deck Freezer Case (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Dual-Jet Protective Devices (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Dual-Jet Kysor & Marshall Nozzles (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Dual-Jet Royal Platindustri Tests (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Dual-Jet Tracers (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Dual-Jet Supersaturation (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Methane Photographs Vol.1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Methane (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Methane Photographs & Report (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Helicopter (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Helicopter (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Helicopter (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Helicopter Photographs (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Helicopter Photographs (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Helicopter Flex Shaft (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Helicopter (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Helicopter (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Helicopter Articles & Reports (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Helicopter Andrew MacGinitie (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Helicopter (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Helicopter Discover Magazine (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Helicopter Sikorski Contest, Manpowered Helicopter (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Helicopter Jet Thrust- Stored Energy (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Helicopter SRI Transportation Report (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Helicopter Blade Data (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - High Speed Ground Transportation (HSGT) 12/1970 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - HSGT (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - HSGT -ASME (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - HSGT (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - HSGT SRI Contract (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - HSGT (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - HSGT Transportation Committee (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - HSGT (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Beckwith Economics Wealth Distribution Charts (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Beckwith Economics Income & Wealth (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Beckwith Economics Income Distribution (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Beckwith Economics (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Beckwith Economics & Computers 1951 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Beckwith Economics Distribution of Income & Capital (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Unigard Insurance Group Fires- Deposition (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Unigard Fires Carmichael (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Unigard Fires Heater, San Francisco (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Unigard Fires Chico (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Unigard Fires Pacifica (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Unigard Fires New Cardinal – Fairfield- Hillsborough (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Unigard Fires Utah St., San Francisco (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Unigard Fires Aptos (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Unigard Fires Galt (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Unigard Fires Corte Madera (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Unigard Fires Sausalito (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Unigard Fires Mill Valley (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Unigard Fires Carmel (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Unigard Fires Pacific Grove (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Unigard Fires Modesto (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Unigard Fires Hursh vs. Winnenago (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Unigard Fires Implanter (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Unigard Fires Auburn (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Unigard Fires Train Transformers (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Unigard Fires (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Beckwith Engineering Articles (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings "I Beg To Differ" (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings "I Beg To Differ" Bound Essays (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings Generation Gap- Alumni Survey (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings "Haves & Have-Nots" (Old) (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings Generation Gap (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings "Helping My Neighbor" (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings Hutchins Rewrite (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings Old Project Summary (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings First Book, Original (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Funny File Articles (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings "Lynching of a President" (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Beckwith Opinions & Writings Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - General Atomic Co. (GAC) Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - GAC Meeting Notes (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - GAC Doublet III System 2 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - GAC Installation 1976 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - GAC Doublet II (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - GAC Report & Drawings (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - GAC (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - GAC Doublet III Data (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - GAC Related Specs (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - GAC (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - GAC Old Specs (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - GAC Latest Specs (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - GAC Doublet III Poloidal & Toroidal Specs (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - GAC PF of Rectifiers (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - GAC Reports (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Water District of Southern California (MWD) Castaic (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - MWD Castaic Syn-Mach Articles (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - MWD Castaic (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - MWD Castaic General Plans (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - MWD Castaic (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - MWD Castaic Stability Study 1933 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - MWD Castaic Lake Matthews (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - MWD Castaic Foothills Tests 1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - MWD Castaic San Dimas (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - MWD Castaic Power Recovery (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - MWD Castaic Articles (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - MWD Tehachapi- DMJM, W, GE (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - MWD Tehachapi- DMJM (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - MWD Tehachapi Westinghouse (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - MWD Tehachapi- DMJM (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - EPRI (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Mower (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Psychrometric chart (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Rake (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Vacuum Brake (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Vacuum Brake (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Vacuum Brake Active (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Vacuum Brake Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Vacuum Brake (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Vacuum Brake (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Stockyards Patents (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - MWD Nitrous Oxide- Nitrafix (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Nitrafix (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Guided Vehicle (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Square Wave (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Square Wave (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Air Conditioning- New (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Water From Air (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Wind Power- Caltech (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Wind Power Specs & Schedule (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Argonne National Laboratory (Specs) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Nitrafix (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Fuel Cell Kit (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Variable Speed Motor (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - PG&E Stanislaus Generator (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Vehicle Drive (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Air Cushion (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Crib (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Turbochiller DTC (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Turbochiller (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Turbochiller Mixing (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Turbochiller DTC- Electrolux (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Turbochiller DTC Shrink Curves (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Magnetohydrodynamic Power Generator (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Wind Power Lockheed (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - HSGT- ASME (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Transportation (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Beckwith Articles, Manuals (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes- Science (Beckwith Library) (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes- Science (Beckwith Library) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Stock Yards Research Division, 1956: blueprints (Folder os folder)
  - Paradise [CA] Irrigation District [re Water Distribution System], 1982: blueprints (Box Roll 1)
  - Dual-Jet #22 Temp Tests, June 25, 26, 29-July 2,7,9,10, 1970: graphs (Box Roll 2)
  - % Favorable to Continued Use of 1928 BCP vs. Per Cent Favorable to Alternative Use of 1928 Book of Common Prayer [re 1976-77 polls]: graph, y vs. x-axes (Box Roll 3)